Looks like him and Alex
are agents working against us.
And when that happens
Mikoy will be dead.
Why are you calling?
Didn't you say
I shouldn't answer this phone?
This is urgent and I need
to talk to you right away.
Why? What's wrong?
Mikoy, listen to me carefully.
You need to stay away from Chiara.
And what they're planning to do next.
No, you're wrong.
Okay. What you're saying is impossible.
Because Chiara is in Prague.
I knew you'd say that.
But it's better if we meet in person
and I'll explain everything there.
But for now, I need
to secure your safety first.
Because she might already be
making a move against you.
I'll message you the location.
Mikoy, What's wrong?
Why are you reacting like that?
I need to meet with Alex.
I'll come with you.
I'm coming too.
No, stay here.
I'm going alone.
What are you talking about?
I'm coming with you
whether you like it or not.
Dad.
No.
I know I've said things
you weren't supposed to know.
But that doesn't mean
you have to get involved in this.
Dad, you can't get dragged into this.
So please, just let me handle it.
This is my fight.
Mikoy. This isn't just your fight.
You're a Pinagpala.
We're all Pinagpala.
This is our fight.
But not this time.
I won't allow my son
to put himself in danger.
Dad.
It was my decision to get
involved in this mess.
So please trust me
that I can stand by this decision.
And besides, Mom.
She has no idea what's going on.
Dad, we need to protect her.
And if something bad happens to me.
At least I know both of you
will be there for her.
Dad, Mom needs you.
Sianong!
Sofie.
What is really going on?
There was another attempt on your dad.
What?
Where is he? Is he okay?
Don't worry, he was just
talking to Alex earlier.
And trust your dad.
He's sharp.
Sofie.
I'm sorry.
Does it hurt?
Yes, when you hit me.
- It's nothing.
- Dad…
It's far from the intestines, come on.
Stop crying already.
- It's always "far from the intestines."
- I'm fine.
I know you.
Look at this, it's just like an ant bite.
It's nothing.
It hurts!
It's okay. That's enough, stop crying.
- Come on.
- It's always "okay."
I'm okay now, okay?
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm okay.
Sir.
Is Alex not with you?
Angelito.
Whatever you know right now.
No one else should know about it.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, sir.
Because this is the best way
to protect your brother.
By keeping these secrets hidden.
I understand, Dad.
No one should know, not even your mother.
You mean to say…
- I'll lie to Mom?
- You're not going to lie.
There are just things you don't say
or tell her.
Okay.
And this is also the best way
for you to protect yourself.
If someone finds out
that you know the truth.
Believe it or not.
Many people want the truth dead.
Kian.
Bro.
Do you know where Alex is?
I didn't notice.
Mikoy might…
Hey.
Alex sent her here.
Sir, the agent escaped from us.
Idiots!
The task I gave you was so simple.
But we'll still look for her.
Viktor.
If things are already this messy
here in the Philippines
let's go back to Prague.
It's still our home, right?
Thank you for all your help.
If you still need anything.
Just let me know.
You're not the one who hurt me.
Because I let myself
drown in this illusion.
I lost touch with reality.
I learned the hard way.
What's your plan?
I will make sure.
Everyone who betrayed me will pay!
Where are you? Are you home?
No, what about you? Are you still out?
She said I've been gone for too long.
What about you?
Sounds like you're out too.
Yes. I'm at a restaurant right now.
It's too quiet at home so,
I had to go out.
It depresses me there.
Don't worry.
When I get home.
I'll cook for you again.
The kind of food you'll never forget.
Wow, I miss that already.
I miss your cooking, sweetheart.
Since you’re not here.
I hope I can see you soon too.
Who were you talking to?
Chiara.
And she's in Prague.
So what you're saying is impossible.
She was at Sir Norberto's house earlier.
How are you so sure it was Chiara?
Do you have evidence?
We are still processing the scene.
So we have forensic traces of her.
No, that's impossible.
She could never do that.
Really?
You actually believe what you're saying?
Zero possibility
that Chiara is capable of being
La Fornarina?
Like some innocent little saint?
Unlike you, I'm not blind.
I'm not blind to what I feel for her.
And I can clearly see
what kind of person she is.
It's not easy to see.
It's not easy to notice.
Because she's good at hiding
who she really is.
But no matter what she does.
The stench of what she's hiding
will eventually come out.
And that's her true nature.
Can you really say that you know Chiara?
I know this is shocking
and hard to believe.
But this isn't just suspicion, Mikoy.
Carlota already confirmed it.
The same Carlota, the secretary
Viktor planted around you.
The secretary you thought was the enemy.
The same secretary we initially
suspected to be La Fornarina.
She is not La Fornarina.
And now she's our state witness.
And now she's on our side.
Stop closing your eyes to it.
The most dangerous Moraviano
is already right in front of you.
Open your eyes to the truth
that the biggest enemy here
is the person you love.
That's enough.
Mikoy.
I said that's enough!
Mikoy!
Mikoy.
Don't be stupid.
The first time I saw you
you were the one who said
never to underestimate you.
People shouldn’t treat you as dumb
for not finishing school.
And I believed you.
In the short time I've known you,
I've come to realize how smart you are.
Mikoy, I know you're intelligent.
And I know your heart already knows
what the truth really is.
That you've made the biggest
mistake of loving someone
who doesn't deserve to be loved.
And what do you know about love?
About us?
You know, Chiara was right.
I really should be careful around you.
Are you really that shallow, Alex?
You're doing all of this
just to break us apart?
Just because you like me?
What are you talking about?
We're done.
You know, being a state witness
is a long process.
Because first we need to verify all the
information you're giving us.
It has to be verified,
the sources have to be reliable.
Okay?
It can't be that
you just keep talking nonstop,
keep spilling stories and then we
just nod along to everything you feed us.
You still have a long way to go.
But for the meantime
we'll transfer you first to one
of our safe houses.
You know, for safety.
Cutie, you know…
You're hard to read too.
You like Agent Alex, don't you?
Okay, believe it or not.
The relationship Alex and I have
it's purely professional.
Sure. That's a lot of talking.
Got it already
and yet you still keep explaining.
I hope you're the one
assigned to guard me.
You know, my bodyguard at the safe house.
You know what I hope?
Especially the innocent
people getting dragged in
because of the mess the
Moravianos brought.
The mess you all brought!
I already gave Agent Alex
the most important information
that I have.
I already revealed the true
identity of La Fornarina.
Who?
But it's none other than
the beloved of Pinagpala.
Impossible.
Too impossible. I won't believe that.
You know what's impossible?
For you to believe
that Mikoy is still your loyal asset.
He's already tasted the Moraviano life.
He's fallen.
Deeply fallen.
Madly in love with the Valtrovi girl.
Do you really think
the information he's giving you
is still truthful?
All of you are too naive
if you think you can't be manipulated
by Viktor and Chiara
through your lover boy asset.
Do you remember this?
We used to do this all the time in Prague.
Chiara?
Dear.
Chiara.
What happened?
My child.
Child…
Who are you really?!
My child.
Mama!
Mom!
Well, she managed to get some rest.
Nothing. She's not saying anything.
Nada.
Whatever it is
all I know is she's deeply hurt.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
The last time I saw her like this.
Was when…
Chiara, my child.
Why?
Bro!
Are you okay?
Did something happen?
Mikoy.
Angelito and I talked.
We know you're the only asset
connected to G.A.G.O.
But we think
we can still help in many ways.
Dad, let's talk about that some other day.
I just want to be alone for now.
We'll be here.
Why are you calling?
Didn't you say
that I shouldn't answer this phone?
Mikoy, listen to me carefully.
You need to stay away from Chiara.
Stop closing your eyes to it.
The most dangerous Moraviano
is already right in front of you.
You’re the one who has to stand down!
Why don’t you try?
Try to disarm me and we’ll see!
You’re too…
- What is happening here?!
- attached to Mikoy.
Whatever this is Brusko, drop it.
You’re hiding the truth from me.
So, let me remind you.